Finding Aid for Frank Manny papers 1890-1955
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Journals
  - Typewritten
    - 1943-1950, 6 volumes (Box 6)
Sept. 10, 1892; Oct. 4, 1895; Jan. 4, 1896; Jan. 16, 1896; Jan. 25, 1896; Mar. 4, 1896; Mar. 11, 1896; Mar. 16, 1896; Mar. 26, 1896 (2); Apr. 9, 1896, Apr. 17, 1896; May 10, 1896; May 17, 1896; May 26, 1896; June 20, 1896, July 8; 1896; July 22, 1896; July 25, 1896; July 28, 1896; Aug. 2, 1896; Aug. 11, 1896; Aug. 16, 1896; Sept. 4, 1896; Sept. 9, 1896, Sept. 14, 1896 (2), Sept. 1896; May 7, 1897; June 7, 1897; June 15, 1897; June 22, 1897; June 29, 1897; July 16, 1897; Nov. 29, 1897; Nov. 30, 1897; Dec. 20, 1897; Feb. 27, 1898; Mar. 21, 1898; May 11, 1898; Sept. 8, 1898; Sept. 22, 1898; Nov. 16, 1898; Mar. 26, 1899; July 26, 1899; Sept. 12, 1899; Nov. 1, 1899; Nov. 23, 1899; Dec. 11, 1899; Jan. 8, 1900; Jan. 18, 1900; Jan. 23, 1900; Feb. 10, 1900; Mar. 3, 1900; Mar. 9, 1900; Apr. 17, 1900; Apr. 25, 1900; May 18, 1900; June 8, 1900; June 18, 1900; Sept. 12, 1900; Oct. 4, 1900; Jan. 7, 1901; Feb. 18, 1901; Mar. 31, 1901; May 10, 1901; May 24, 1901, Nov. 1, 1901; Jan. 17, 1902; Jan. 29, 1902; Feb. 5, 1902; Mar. 7, 1902; Apr. 22, 1902; June 3, 1902; Oct. 3, 1903; Oct. 20, 1903; Oct. 29, 1903; Nov. 16, 1903; Feb. 24, 1904; Mar. 14, 1904; Mar. 26, 1904; Apr. 29, 1904; May 9, 1904; Feb. 6, 1905; Feb. 17, 1905; Apr. 4, 1905; May 9, 1905; May 11, 1905; May 21, 1905; Oct. 4, 1905; Feb. 16, 1906; May 26, 1906; June 6, 1906; June 23, 1906; Oct. 17, 1907; Sept. 6, 1908; Oct. 25, 1908; Oct. 15, 1909; Nov. 18, 1909; Jan. 20, 1910; Dec. 24, 1910; Mar. 9, 1911; Dec. 20, 1911; Feb. 11, 1915; Feb. 11, 1929; Nov. 5, 1929; Jan. 2, 1931; Feb. 28, 1934; Nov. 21, 1935; Oct. 29, 1936; June 18, 1938; Mar. 5, 1939; Mar. 13, 1939; Feb. 20, 1940; May 28, 1940
Dieffenbach, Albert C.
Dec. 15, 1929
D'Ooge, Martin Luther, 1839-1915.
Aug. 20, 1892; July 8, 1895
Dresser, Horatio Willis, 1866-1954.
May 1, 1903
Dubois, William Edward Burghardt, 1868-1963.
Dec. 29, 1942
Dunbar, Daphne.
Aug. 9, 1937
Dutton, Samuel Train, 1849-1919.
May 15, 1908; Oct. 7, 1911
Dykema, Peter William, 1873-1951.
Aug. 10, 1895; Jan. 31, 1896; July 28, 1897; May 3, 1901; Mar. 30, 1909; Apr. 24, 1909; June 18, 1909; Nov. 7, 1909; Feb. 28, 1910; Oct. 5, 1910; Oct. 22, 1910; Nov. 13, 1911; Jan. 23, 1913
Eastman, Max Forrester, 1893-.
June 17, 1938
Easton, Emily.
July 30, 1930
Edgell, George Harold, 1887-1954.
Dec. 17, 1930
Eliot, Thomas Hopkinson, 1907-.
Dec. 29, 1942
Engel, Leonard.
July 10, 1942
English, Colin.
Jan. 14, 1944
Evans, Elizabeth (Glendower).
Nov. 4, 1926
Farrell, Charles H., 1873-.
Nov. 16, 1910
Fisher, Dorothy (Canfield), 1879-1958.
Dec. 19, 1919; Oct. 29, 1930; Nov. 27, 1933; June 13, 1939; Sept. 16, 1939; July 6, 1942; Feb. 24, 1944; June 23, 1944; July 7, 1944; Feb. 6, 1945
Flexner, Abraham, 1866-.
Mar. 29, 1909
Folks, Homer, 1867-1963.
Mar. 6, 1908
Frank, Glenn, 1887-1940.
June 3, 1925
Frank, Waldo David, 1889-.
Jan. 7, 1926
Frankfurter, Felix, 1882-.
Feb. 13, 1936; Mar. 20, 1939
Fuess, Claude Moore, 1885-1963.
Jan. 5, 1932
Garland, Hamlin, 1860-1940.
Jan. 5, 1940
Gavit, John Palmer, 1868-1954.
Dec. 10, 1917
Gibson, Emily S. (Gilbert).
Nov. 8, 1899
Gleason, Arthur Huntington, 1878-1923.
Jan. 21, 1913
Goodspeed, Charles E.
Aug. 23, 1924
Graham, Frank Porter, 1886-.
Jan. 22, 1936; Dec. 6, 1943
Granstead, Durnard. 1
Mar. 30, 1930
Grant, Wilbur H.
July 22, 1912
Guerard, Albert Leon, 1880-1959.
Feb. 4, 1944; Nov. 16, 1944
Hailmann, William Nicholas, 1836-1930.
Mar. 20, 1909
Hall, Granville Stanley, 1846-1924.
Oct. 14, 1909
Halsey, R.H.
Nov. 7, 1902
Hard, Anne.
Dec. 29, 1930
Hard, William, 1878-1962.
Jan. 15, 1931
Hapgood, Norman, 1868-1937.
Feb. 15, 1931
Harper, William Rainey, 1856-1906.
June 20, 1894
Hart, Joseph Kinmort, 1876-1949.
Sept. 27, 1921; May 6, 1933
Hartzell, Mrs. Morton C.
Sept. 25, 1918; Oct. 17, 1918
Haynes, Royal Storrs.
Jan. 10, 1918
Henderson, C. Hanford.
Nov. 7, 1904
Herrick, Chessman Abiah, 1866-1956.
Dec. 16, 1929
Herron, George Davis, 1862-1925.
Jan. 13, 1893; Mar. 17, 1893; Dec. 21, 1893; Jan. 3, 1894; Mar. 10, 1894; May 24, 1895
Heyward, Dubose, 1885-1940.
Apr. 27, 1940
Hicks, Granville, 1901-.
Mar. 23, 1930; June 19, 1940
Higginson, Mary P. (Thacher), 1844-1941.
Feb. 26, 1919
Hocking, William Ernest, 1873-.
Feb. 14, 1930
Holbrook, Stewart Hall, 1893-.
Jan. 13, 1943; May 30, 1943
Holtzoff, Alexander, 1886-.
Nov. 21, 1942
Hopkins, Ernest Martin, 1877-.
Aug. 26, 1927; Jan. 10, 1928; Mar. 4, 1931; Mar. 20, 1931
Howe, A.A. DeWolfe.
Aug. 3, 1930
Hoxie, Robert Franklin, 1868-1916.
Dec. 22, 1915
Hunt, Jean Lee.
Nov. 8, 1913
James, Edward Janes, 1855-1925.
Mar. 1, 1915
James, Howard M.
Feb. 3, 1933
Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.
Feb. 17, 1914; Feb. 20, 1934
Johnston, Eric A.
Jan. 26, 1943
Kelley, Florence, 1859-1932.
Apr. 18, 1896; May 26, 1896; Nov. 29, 1897; Nov. 14, 1900
Kidd, Thomas I.
Feb. 9, 1899
Kirstein, Louis Edward, 1867-1942.
Mar. 2, 1929
LeFetra, Linnaeus E.
Jan. 2, 1918
Lane, Gertrude.
Aug. 28, 1919
Lane, Rose (Wilder), 1887-.
Jan. 12, 1927
Lanier, Mrs. Chalres D.
Nov. 20, 1913
Laski, Harold Joseph, 1893-1950.
Sept. 5, 1919
Lafavour, Henry, 1862-1946.
Apr. 9, 1918
Lerner, Max, 1902-.
May 26, 1938; Nov. 28, 1938; Nov. 27, 1939; Dec. 13, 1939; Feb. 14, 1940; Feb. 12, 1942; Apr. 7, 1944; Nov. 6, 1944; June 19, 1945
Lewisohn, Ludwig, 1883-1955.
Nov. 16, 1909
Lilienthal, David Eli, 1899-.
Nov. 2, 1938; July 15, 1940
Linville, Henry R.
Nov. 1, 1929; Feb. 3, 1930
Lippman, Walter, 1889-.
Mar. 4, 1913; Mar. 11, 1913; May 19, 1925
Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1902-.
Feb. 22, 1939
Lord, Russell, 1895-.
Nov. 1, 1938
Lovett, Robert Morss, 1870-1956.
Feb. 19, 1936
Lowell, Abbott Lawrence, 1856-1943.
Nov. 19, 1929
MacLean, Eugene.
May 5, 1934
MacLeish, Archibald, 1892-.
June 19, 1940
MacMillan, D. P.
Jan. 19, 1910
MacNeill, Ben Dixon, 1889-1960.
Dec. 31, 1935
Malone, Dumas, 1892-.
Nov. 17, 1942
Mann, Charles Riborg, 1869-1942.
Jan. 21, 1909
Marks, Jeanette.
Mar. 24, 1930
Marshall, Margaret.
May 23, 1939
Martin, George Henry, 1841-1917.
Nov. 2, 1909
Marquand, John Phillips, 1893-1960.
Apr. 9, 1937
Mather, Kirtley Fletcher, 1888-.
Aug. 10, 1937
Mead, George Herbert, 1863-1931.
Oct. 11, 1895; June 11, 1899; June 26, 1899; 1908-1909
Meilklejohn, Alexander, 1872-.
Feb. 6, 1929
Mertz, David Franklin, -1900.
Mar. 6, 1895
Metcalf, Elinor (Gregory).
Feb. 27, 1933; July 31, 1944
Mills, Benjamin Fay, 1857-1916.
Jan. 15, 1894
Monroe, Paul, 1869-1947.
Nov. 22, 1909
Morgan, Arthur Ernest, 1878-.
Feb. 25, 1927
Morgan, James.
Feb. 18, 1929; Mar. 11, 1932
Morison, Samuel Eliot, 1887-.
Mar. 16, 1928
Morley, Felix Muskett, 1894-.
May 4, 1934
Morris, Lloyd, 1893-1954.
Jan. 11, 1944; Feb. 27, 1944
Mott, John Raleigh, 1865-1955.
Dec. 16, 1890; Aug. 17, 1892; Dec. 26, 1892; Jan. 3, 1893; Jan. 30, 1893; Feb. 27, 1893; Apr. 19, 1893; May 18, 1893
Muldoon, William.
Oct. 30, 1905
Mumford, Lewis, 1895-.
Oct. 23, 1927
Munsterberg, Margaret.
Aug. 4, 1930
Murrg, F.M.
June 20, 1910
Mussey, Henry Raymond, 1875-1940.
Dec. 14, 1917
Nichols, Walter Hammond, 1866-1935.
Nov. 28, 1892
Oppenheim, James, 1882-1932.
Oct. 23, 1900; 1905-1915; 1918-1920
O'Shea, Michael Vincent, 1866-1932.
Jan. 14, 1899; June 11, 1900
Palmer, Frank Herbert, 1853-1936.
Dec. 15, 1927
Palmer, George Herbert, 1842-1933.
Mar. 26, 1928
Parker, Francis Wayland, 1837-1902.
May 5, 1897; Sept. 11, 1897; July 10, 1899; July 18, 1899; July 22, 1899
Partridge, Bellamy.
July 27, 1932
Patten, Simon Nelson, 1852-1922.
Oct. 23, 1905; May 29, 1911
Payne, Enoch George, 1877-1953.
Sept. 24, 1910
Pearle, Edward E.
Apr. 1, 1930; Apr. 10, 1930
Peattie, Donald Culross, 1898-.
Apr. 4, 1938
Perry, Clarence Arthur, 1872-1944.
Jan. 17, 1930
Perry, Maude (Caldwell).
Feb. 26, 1930
Phelps, William Lyon, 1865-1943.
Apr. 14, 1927; Feb. 15. 1928
Phillips, James Duncan.
Oct. 26, 1943
Porter, Kenneth.
Apr. 11, 1944
Pressey, Edward Pearson.
Mar. 28, 1908
Price, Lucien, 1883-1964.
Apr. 17, 1926; Mar. 18, 1930; Mar. 25, 1930
Putnam, Elizabeth (Lowell).
Jan. 18, 1927
Rannellis, B.U.
Oct. 3, 1900
Richardson, Hilary G.
Nov. 13, 1929
Rogers, Will, 1911-.
Dec. 9, 1943
Rolfe, John Carew, 1859-1943.
Apr. 24, 1893
Roosevelt, James, 1907-.
Aug. 23, 1937
Roper, Richard F.
May 25, 1934
Rowe, Stuart H.
Nov. 25, 1912
Rugg, Winnifred (King).
Mar. 9, 1930
Rumely, Edward A.
May 28, 1908
Russell, James Earl, 1864-1945.
Jan. 21, 1897; Oct. 9, 1907; Feb. 22, 1908
Saint-Gaudens, Homer Schiff, 1880-1958.
July 2, 1915; Oct. 23, 1930
Sancton, Thomas Wolfe, 1915-.
Feb. 11, 1943
Sanford, Daniel Sammis, 1859-1936.
Aug. 8, 1930
Sargent, Walter, 1868-1927.
Mar. 30, 1911
Savage, Toy Dixon, 1878-1941.
Jan. 14, 1930
Saxon, Lyle, 1891-1946.
Mar. 20, 1930
Sayre, Francis Bowes, 1885-.
Mar. 5, 1929
Schaeffer, Mary F.
Feb. 13, 1902
Schwartz-Buys, E.
Mar. 22, 1929
Scott, Fred Newton, 1860-1931.
Oct. 15, 1894; Dec. 7, 1894; Sept. 17, 1895; Nov. 1, 1895; Nov. 19, 1895; Jan. 6, 1896; Mar. 16, 1898; Aug. 16, 1910
Scudder, Myron Tracy, 1860-1935.
May 17, 1901; Apr. 1, 1908
Seabrook, William Buehler, 1886-1945.
Oct. 15, 1935
Seashore, Carl Emil, 1866-1949.
Aug. 10, 1910
Sedgwick, Ellery, 1872-1960.
July 27, 1928
Seymour, Charles, 1885-1963.
Oct. 23, 1943; Oct. 18, 1945
Shaw, Paula A.
Feb. 14, 1908
Shepard, Odell, 1884-.
June 20, 1937
Sinclair, Upton
Undated (folder 4)
Slosson, Edwin Emery, 1865-1929.
Oct. 5, 1907
Slosson, Preston William, 1892-.
June 10, 1942
Snedden, David.
Oct. 17, 1910
South, Lloyd V.
May 1, 1901
Smith, Glanville.
July 30, 1935
Smith, Lillian E., 1897-.
Feb. 4, 1943
Smith, Thomas Vernor, 1890-.
Feb. 8, 1939
Spencer, Anna (Garlin), 1851-1931.
Oct. 16, 1912
Stark, Otto, 1859-1926.
Apr. 5, 1897
Steele, Thomas Clement, 1847-1926.
Mar. 23, 1905
Stein, Clarence S., 1882-.
May 23, 1925
Storrow, Helen (Osborn).
Mar. 1908
Suzzallo, Henry, 1875-1933.
May 5, 1909
Swift, Edgar James, 1860-1932.
Jan. 30, 1900
Talbert, Edward.
Mar. 6, 1910
Talbot, Marion, 1858-1948.
Jan. 19, 1910
Tarbell, Ida Minerva, 1857-1944.
June 6, 1932; June 30, 1939
Taylor, Graham, 1851-1938.
Oct. 10, 1900; Jan. 6, 1902
Thomas, Lowell, 1892-.
Jan. 10, 1933
Todd, J. Liberty.
Jan. 21, 1899
Traubel, Horace, 1858-1919.
May 4, 1905
Triggs, Oscar L.
Sept. 8, 1905; Oct. 9, 1905
Tyner, Paul.
Apr. 29, 1899
Untermeyer, Louis, 1885-.
Mar. 19, 1927
Valbin, Joseph.
Nov. 25, 1938
Van Doren, Mark, 1894-.
Apr. 9, 1931
Villard, Oswald Garrison, 1872-1949.
Nov. 14, 1928; June 9, 1929; Jan. 30, 1936
Vincent, George Edgar, 1864-1941.
Aug. 6, 1900; July 28, 1911
Walm, Nora, 1895-.
Apr. 30, 1939
Walsh, David Ignatius, 1872-1947.
Oct. 26, 1938
Washington, Booker Taliaferro, 1856-1915.
Apr. 6, 1908
Watson, Goodwin Barbour, 1899-.
Apr. 21, 1939
Weygandt, Cornelius.
May 19, 1930; July 2, 1930; July 10, 1930; Aug. 26, 1930; Sept. 9, 1930
Whipple, Guy Montrose, 1876-1941.
Aug. 2, 1909; Dec. 20, 1911
White, Stewart Edward, 1873-1946.
Feb. 8, 1906; Oct. 28, 1926
Whiting, Lilian, 1859-1942.
May 9, 1919
Wieffenbach, Albert C.
Dec. 26, 1936
Wilcox, Delos Franklin, 1873-1928.
Aug. 18, 1891; Aug. 1, 1892; Aug. 9, 1892; Aug. 11, 1892; June 25, 1893; July 9, 1893; July 31, 1893; Sept. 6, 1893; Sept. 7, 1893; Sept. 11, 1893; Sept. 1893; July 25, 1894; July 28, 1894; Aug. 9, 1894; Aug. 15, 1894; Sept. 6, 1894; Sept. 30, 1894; Oct. 14, 1894; Oct. 25, 1894; Oct. 31, 1894; Nov. 18, 1894; Nov. 27, 1894; Dec. 2, 1894; Dec. 5, 1894; Dec. 14, 1894; Dec. 27, 1894; Jan. 3, 1895; Jan. 7, 1895; Jan. 18, 1895; Jan. 20, 1895; Feb. 9, 1895; Mar. 1, 1895; Mar. 21, 1895; Apr. 16, 1895; Apr. 30, 1895; May 8, 1895; June 22, 1895; May 23, 1895; July 19, 1895; Aug. 17, 1895; Sept. 2, 1895; Sept. 28, 1895; Oct. 6, 1895; Oct. 25, 1895; Dec. 8, 1895; Dec. 22, 1895
Jan. 10, 1896; Mar. 8, 1896; Apr. 15, 1896; Apr. 25, 1896; June 10, 1896; June 24, 1896; July 3, 1896; Sept. 15, 1896; Oct. 15, 1896; Nov. 1, 1896; Dec. 11, 1896; Jan. 22, 1897; Feb. 24, 1897; Mar. 3, 1897; Mar. 27, 1897; May 23, 1897; June 20, 1897; Aug. 8, 1897; Sept. 4, 1897; Nov. 25, 1897; Dec. 22, 1897; Feb. 24, 1898; May 16, 1898; Mar. 18, 1898; Apr. 10, 1898; May 18, 1898; June 16, 1898; June 19, 1898; Oct. 27, 1898; Nov. 7, 1898; Jan. 23, 1899; Feb. 8, 1899; Mar. 23, 1899; Apr. 19, 1899; June 8, 1899; June 13, 1899; June 15, 1899; July 2, 1899; Aug. 26, 1899; Oct. 4, 1899; Oct. 8, 1899; Nov. 11, 1899; Nov. 20, 1899; Nov. 26, 1899; Dec. 17, 1899; Dec. 26, 1899; Feb. 15, 1900; Mar. 12, 1900; Mar. 15, 1900; Mar. 30, 1900; Apr. 1, 1900; Apr. 29, 1900; May 10, 1900; June 22, 1900; Jan. 24, 1901; Mar. 8, 1901; Mar. 31, 1901; May 9, 1901; May 12, 1901; June 13, 1901; Sept. 8, 1901; Nov. 4, 1901; Jan. 15, 1902; Mar. 30, 1902; Apr. 15, 1902.
Wilson, Edmund, 1895-.
July 8, 1937; Mar. 20, 1948
Wilson, Woodrow, Pres. U.S., 1856-1924.
May 20, 1905
Wolfe, Rolland Emerson, 1902-.
July 19, 1944; May 28, 1947
Woodberry, George Edward, 1855-1930.
Dec. 22, 1904
Woodbridge, Homer Edwards, 1882-1958.
Jan. 1, 1930
Woodward, Comer Vann, 1906-.
Feb. 9, 1940
Woolf, Virginia.
Aug. 23, 1939
Yarmolinsky, Avrahm, 1890-.
Jan. 27, 1943, Aug. 5, 1945
Young, Ella (Flagg), 1845-1918.
Jan. 28, 1908; Mar. 13, 1911
Zelenko, A.V.
Apr. 30, 1919
Zueblin, Charles, 1866-1924.
Apr. 21, 1908; Oct. 30, 1911